cutouthunger.org 2004-10-10

# Cut your grocery bill in half and feed the hungry with cutouthunger.org. Money saving coupons from Smartsource, Coolsavings, and money saving offers from local grocery stores, Upromise and Babymint.

**  
** Cut Out Hunger, Inc. Privacy Policy 

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Cut Out Hunger, Inc. is committed to protecting your personal privacy. We provide this notice to explain the type of information we collect on the **www.cutouthunger.org** website and how we use this information. This Policy also explains the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Our Privacy Policy is available for you to review on our homepage and at every site where we have requested personally identifiable information. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
You may be asked to provide personal information so that you can register to receive coupons, participate in a sweepstakes or contest, receive information, fill out a survey, or join a club. Your participation is voluntary and we will not require you to provide more information than is necessary to participate in any of our current or future website's activities. In some instances, we may ask you questions on an aggregate basis (we don't identify you personally with the information) and such questions will be identified on the website. In all other instances, you should assume that we will track any information you provide on a personally identifiable basis. The types of personal information collected on this website includes: i) name; ii) address; iii) e-mail address; iv) demographic data; v) preferential data and other information that will help us better serve your consumer patterns. 

Cut Out Hunger, Inc. does not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. 

**The Way We Use Information**

Cutouthunger.org provides you with the opportunity to register on the site through the Registration section. Registration is required to be eligible to receive savings offers, enter any of the online contests or sweepstakes. Cutouthunger.org may use the information you provide when registering to fulfill prizes. 

When you register with our website, you can elect to receive information and updates on our products and services. Information will not be used for this purpose unless you request to receive Cutouthunger.org communications or communications from our business partners. 

We use information that you provide (individual and aggregate) to better design our website and to improve our marketing strategy and our products. One method through which this website collects aggregate information is the collection of IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from this website, our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us. To the extent such information is shared with third parties, please see "Our Privacy Practices With Third Parties" below. 

Occasionally, you will have the opportunity to forward pages or information on the site to friends. The information you provide to facilitate this email communication is used on a one-time basis and is not collected or retained by Cutouthunger.org. 

**Unsubscribe/Delete**  
Cutouthunger.org gives users the following options for managing or removing their information from our database: 

1\. Send us an email: Send an email to [postmaster@cutouthunger.org](mailto:postmaster@cutouthunger.org). Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you would like us to do. 

2\. Manage Your Cutouthunger.org Profile: Within the Registration section of Cutouthunger.org you have the option to Manage Your Cutouthunger.org Profile. The Cutouthunger.org management system allows you to update or delete your information from our database. We also allow you to subscribe or unsubscribe to any of the promotional email updates we send out. 

**Our Privacy Practices with Third Parties**  
We share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not provide any identifiable personal information to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless you register or subscribe for their services. 

Our intention is never to use or share personally identifiable information provided to us in ways that are different than the ways described above without also providing you with an opportunity to "unsubscribe" or prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Users should be aware that when you are on this website you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There may be links to other sites that take you outside our service. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use the Cutouthunger.org logo. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. Check the linked site to locate its Privacy Policy, which may be different from our own. If the Cutouthunger.org website links you to any third party website, Cutouthunger.org makes no representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their Privacy Policy. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security:**  
We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

**Changes in Our Policy**  
We reserve the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post those changes here. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. If there is any material change in the type of information we collect, we will obtain your permission before we attempt to collect the additional personal information from your child. We will not make any changes, which allow us to give personal information to a third party without obtaining permission from you first. 

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**  
By using this website, you signify your assent to the Cutouthunger.org, Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the collection of information, please e-mail us at: [postmaster@cutouthunger.org](mailto:info@cutouthunger.org)
